Dear  {FirstName} {LastName},

Thank you for submitting your details for the role of vacancy at {CompanyName} (ref: {VacancyProjectId}).

Please see attached the candidate brochure for the vacancy along with any relevant attachments.

Please note, you have not applied for this role, when you decide to complete this application, please use the link below to:

{GeneratedLink}

If you need any further information, please get in touch,

Best wishes,

Perrett Laver