Dear  {FirstName} {LastName},

Re: {VacancyTitle}, {CompanyName}


Thank you very much for your interest in the above appointment. Having reviewed the full field of candidates with {CompanyName}, I’m afraid we are coming back with what may be disappointing news as they have decided not to pursue your application further on this occasion. There were a number of strong applications for this position, and they have progressed a small number of candidates whose particular sets of experience and skills meet the client’s needs more closely.


I am sorry to not have a more positive outcome on this occasion, but we are grateful for your time in considering this position and hope that we might have the opportunity to stay in touch in the future.


Kind regards,

Perrett Laver