Dear {FirstName},

Thank you for your application for the role of {VacancyTitle} at {CompanyName} (ref: {VacancyProjectId}). We appreciate the time you have taken to apply, and this email is to confirm that we have received your application.

We will review this with our client in due course. Once this meeting has taken place, we will be in contact to let you know whether they wish to progress your application further.

The candidate brochure is currently being finalised and we will send the document through to you in due course.

With best wishes,

Perrett Laver
