Dear {FirstName} {LastName},

Thank you for submitting your details for the role of vacancy - {CompanyName} (ref: {VacancyProjectId}). The candidate brochure is currently being finalised and we will send the document through to you in due course.

Please note, you have not applied for this role, when you decide to complete this application, please use the link below to:

{GeneratedLink}

If you need any further information, please get in touch.

Best wishes,

Perrett Laver